Finding Aid for the The Francis Robinson Collection
Special Collections and University Archives
- (The File Description)
  - Operas (C - .1)
    - The Great Waltz (Johann Strauss, Sr. & Jr.) (Box 64, Folder 42)
    - William Tell (Rossini) (Box 64, Folder 43)
    - The Gypsy Baron (Johann Strauss) (Box 64, Folder 44)
    - Les Huguenots (Meyerbeer) (Box 64, Folder 45)
    - Idomeneo (Mozart) (Box 64, Folder 46)
    - L'Incoronazione de Poppea (Verdi) (Box 64, Folder 47)
    - Iris (Mascagni) (Box 64, Folder 48)
    - Ivan Sussanin (Michele Glinka) (Box 64, Folder 49)
    - Jonny Spielt Auf (Ernst Krenek) (Box 64, Folder 50)
    - Julius Caesar (George F. Handel) (Box 64, Folder 51)
  - Operas (K- 0)
    - Katerina Ismailova (Dmitri Shostakovich) (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Khovanshchina (Mussorgsky) (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - The King's Henchamn (Deems Taylor) (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Koanga (Frederick Delius) (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Konsul (Gian-Carlo McnoHi) (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Lakme (Leo Delibes) (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - The Lat Savage (Gian-Carlo Menotti) (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Little Mary Sunshine (Rick Besoyan) (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Lodoletta (Muscugni) (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Lohengrin (Wagner) (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Lord Byron (Virgil Thomson) (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Louise (Gustave Charpentier) (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - Luisa Miller (Verdi) (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - Lulu (Alban Borg) (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - Macbeth (Verdi) (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - Madame Butterfly (Puccini) (Box 65, Folder 16)
    - Manon (Julis Massenet) (Box 65, Folder 17)
    - Manon Lescaut (Puccini) (Box 65, Folder 18)
    - Maritana (Vincent Wallace) (Box 65, Folder 19)
    - Martha (Friderick von Flotow) (Box 65, Folder 20)
    - Mefistofele (Arrigo Boito) (Box 65, Folder 21)
    - Die meistersinger von Nornberg (Wagner) (Box 65, Folder 22)
    - The Merry Widow (Franz Lehar) (Box 65, Folder 23)
    - Mignon (Ambroise Thomas) (Box 65, Folder 24)
    - The Mikado (Box 65, Folder 25)
    - Mona (Horatio Parker) (Box 65, Folder 26)
    - The Mother of Us All (Virgil Thomson) (Box 65, Folder 27)
    - Mourning Becomes Electra (Marrin David Levy) (Box 65, Folder 28)
    - My Maryland (Sigmund Romberg) (Box 65, Folder 29)
    - Nabucco (Verdi) (Box 65, Folder 30)
    - No, No, Nanette (Vincent Youmans) (Box 65, Folder 31)
    - Norma (Vincenzo Bellini) (Box 65, Folder 32)
    - Le Nozze de Figaro (Mozart) (Box 65, Folder 33)
    - Oh! Oh! Deiphine (Ivan Caryll) (Box 65, Folder 34)
    - Opera (Luciano Berio) (Box 65, Folder 35)
    - L'Oradolo (Franco Leoni) (Box 65, Folder 36)
    - Orfeo (Monteverdi) (Box 65, Folder 37)
    - Orfeo ed Evridice (Gluck) (Box 65, Folder 38)
    - Otello (Verdi) (Box 65, Folder 39)
  - Operas (P - S)
    - I Pagliacci ((Ruggiero Leoncavallo) (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - The Pajama Game (Richard Adler and Jerry Ross) (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Parsifal (Wagner) (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - The Passion of Jonathan Wade (Carlisle Floyd) (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Pelleas et Melisande (Claude Debussy) (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - La Perichol (Jacques Offenbach) (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Peter Ibbestson (Deems Taylor) (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Pigue Dame (Tchaikovsky) (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - The Pirates of Penzance (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Porgy and Bess (George Gershwin) (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Prince Igor (Alexander Borodin) (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Le Prophete (Meyerbeer) (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - I Puritan (Bellini) (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - Queen of Sheba (Karl Guldmark) (Box 66, Folder 14)
    - The Rake's Progress (Igor Stravinsky) (Box 66, Folder 15)
    - Das Rheingold (Richard Wagner) (Box 66, Folder 16)
    - Rienzi (Wagner) (Box 66, Folder 17)
    - Rigoletto (Verdi) (Box 66, Folder 18)
    - Der Ring des Nibelungen (Wagner) (Box 66, Folder 19)
    - Romeo et Juliette (Gounod) (Box 66, Folder 20)
    - Rosalinda (Johann Strauss) (Box 66, Folder 21)
    - Der Rosenkavalier (Richard Strauss) (Box 66, Folder 22)
    - Sadko (Rimsky - Korsakov) (Box 66, Folder 23)
    - Salome (Richard Strauss) (Box 66, Folder 24)
    - Samson et Dalila (Camille Saint-Saens) (Box 66, Folder 25)
    - Siegfried (Wagner) (Box 66, Folder 26)
    - Sigurd (Ernest Reyer) (Box 66, Folder 27)
    - Simon Boccanegra (Verdi) (Box 66, Folder 28)
    - Snegurochka (Rimsky - Korsakov) (Box 66, Folder 29)
    - La Sonnambula (Bellimi) (Box 66, Folder 30)
    - Sorochinskaya Yarmarka (Mussorgsky) (Box 66, Folder 31)
    - The Student Prince (Sigmond Romberg) (Box 66, Folder 32)
  - Operas (T - Z)
    - Tannhauser (Wagner) (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Thais (Jules Massenet) (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - This Means, That ... (Luiano Berio) (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Tommy (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Tosca (Puccini) (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - La Traviata (Verdi) (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Trial by Jury (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Tristan un Isolde (Wagner) (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - II Trittico (Puccini) (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Il Trovatore (Verdi) (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Les Troyens (Hector Berlin) (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Turandot (Puccini) (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - Vanessa (Samuel Barber) (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - The Visitation (Gunther Schuller) (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - Die Walkure (Wagner) (Box 67, Folder 15)
    - The Warrior (Bernard Rogers) (Box 67, Folder 16)
    - Werther (Jules Massenet) (Box 67, Folder 17)
    - Wozzeck (Alban Berg) (Box 67, Folder 18)
    - Xerxes (George F. Handel) (Box 67, Folder 19)
    - The Yeomen of the Guard (Arthur Sullivan) (Box 67, Folder 20)
    - Die Zauberflote (Mozart) (Box 67, Folder 21)
    - Zara (Leoncavallo) (Box 67, Folder 22)
  - MET - Radio Broadcasts
    - Radio Broadcast - Misc. (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Radio Broadcast Scripts, 1956-59 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Radio Broadcast Scripts, 1960-61 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Radio Broadcast Scripts, 1962-63 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Radio Broadcast Scripts, 1964-66 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Radio Broadcast Scripts, 1967-68 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Radio Broadcast Scripts, 1969-72 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - A Collector's - Thanksgiving, Christmas, Easter, 1967-79 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - MET - Radio Broadcasts
    - Radio Broadcast Scripts (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Broadcast Advertising, Program Guides (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Radio Broadcast Press Releases (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Radio Broadcast Clippings, 1932-68 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Radio Broadcast Clippings, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Radio Broadcast Clippings, 1970-79; undated items (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - MET - Radio Broadcasts
    - WNCN Clippings - Opera Highlights, May 1969 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - WNCN Clippings - Opera Highlights, Jun. 1969 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - WNCN Clippings - Opera Highlights, Jul. 1969 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - WNCN Clippings - Opera Highlights, Aug. 1969 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - WNCN Clippings - Opera Highlights, Sep. 1969 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - WNCN Clippings - Opera Highlights, Oct. 1969 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - WNCN Clippings - Opera Highlights, Nov. 1969 (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - WNCN Clippings - Opera Highlights, Dec. 1969 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - WNCN Clippings - Opera Highlights, Jan. 1970 (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - WNCN Programs - Opera Highlights, Feb. 1970 (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - WNCN Clippings - Opera Highlights, Mar. 1970 (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - WNCN Clippings - Opera Highlights, Apr. 1970 (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - WNCN Clippings - Opera Highlights, May 1970 (Box 70, Folder 13)
    - WNCN Clippings - Opera Highlights, Jun. 1970 (Box 70, Folder 14)
    - WNCN Clippings - Opera Highlights, Jul. 1970 (Box 70, Folder 14)
    - WNCN Clippings - Opera Highlights, Aug. 1970 (Box 70, Folder 15)
    - WNCN Clippings - Opera Highlights, Sep. 1970 (Box 70, Folder 16)
    - WNCN Clippings - Opera Highlights, Oct. 1970 (Box 70, Folder 17)
    - WNCN Clippings - Opera Highlights, Nov. 1970 (Box 70, Folder 18)
    - WNCN Clippings - Opera Highlights, Dec. 1970 (Box 70, Folder 19)
    - Metropolitan Gala, Apr. 3, 1972 (Box 70, Folder 20)
    - Metropolitan Opera - 100 Years, Dec. 5, 1979 (first draft) (Box 70, Folder 21)
    - Metropolitan Opera - 100 Years, Dec. 13, 1979 (second draft) (Box 70, Folder 22)
    - Metropolitan Opera - 100 Years, Jan. 24, 1980 (working draft) (Box 70, Folder 23)
    - Metropolitan Opera - 100 Years, Jan. 22, 1980 (final draft) (Box 70, Folder 24)
    - Metropolitan Opera - Closed Circuit Telecast, Nov. 8, 1954 (Box 70, Folder 25)
  - MET - Radio Broadcasts (Telecast Scripts)
    - Telecast Scripts (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - MET Telecasts (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Metropolitan Opera Stars on Film - Scripts, Drafts, and Work Notes (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Metropolitan Opera Stars on Film Program (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Metropolitan Opera Stars on Film program and Clippings (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - MET Recordings (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - MET Clippings, 1894 - 1939
    - 1894 - 1909 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - 1910 - 1919 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - 1920 - 1929 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - 1930 - 1939 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Undated items (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - MET Clippings, 1940 - 1961
    - Clippings, 1940 - 1949 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Clippings, 1950 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Clippings, 1951 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Clippings, 1952 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Clippings, 1953 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Clippings, 1954 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Clippings, 1955 (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Clippings, 1956 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Clippings, 1957 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Clippings, 1958 (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - Clippings, 1959 (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - Clippings, 1960 (Box 73, Folder 12)
    - Clippings, 1961 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - MET Clippings, 1962 - 1969
    - Clippings, 1962 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Clippings, 1963 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Clippings, 1964 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Clippings, 1965 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Clippings, Jan. - Aug. 1966 (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Clippings, Sep. - Dec. 1966 (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - Clippings, 1967 (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Clippings, 1968 (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - Clippings, 1969 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - MET Clippings, 1970 - 1979
    - Clippings, 1970 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Clippings, 1971 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Clippings, 1972 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Clippings, 1973 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Clippings, 1974 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Clippings, 1975 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Clippings, 1976 (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - Clippings, 1977 (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - Clippings, 1978 (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - Clippings, 1979 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Metropolitan Opera Opening Nights (1934 -1962)
    - MET Openings, General (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - MET Openings, 1934 - 1949 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - MET Openings, 1950 - 1953 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - MET Openings, 1954 - 1956 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - MET Openings, 1957 - 1959 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - MET Openings, 1960 - 1962 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Metropolitan Opera Opening Nights (1963 -1979)
    - MET Openings, 1963 - 1964 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - MET Openings, 1965 - 1967 (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - MET Openings, 1968 - 1969 (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - MET Openings, 1970 - 1974 (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - MET Openings, 1975 - 1979 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Robinson Photograph Collection (Ab - As)
    - Abbe, Johnny, Patience and Richard (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Abel, Walter (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Adams, Maude (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Adler, Kurt (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Adler, Luther (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Aherne, Brian and de Havilland Olivia (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Aida (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - Akin, Mrs. Thomas (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - Albanese, Licia (Box 78, Folder 9)
    - Alberni, Luis (Box 78, Folder 10)
    - Alda, Frances (Box 78, Folder 11)
    - Aldrich, Richard (Box 78, Folder 12)
    - Alexander, John (Box 78, Folder 13)
    - Alexander, Ross (Box 78, Folder 14)
    - Alford, Walter (Box 78, Folder 15)
    - Algood (Box 78, Folder 16)
    - Allen, Reginald & Helen (Box 78, Folder 17)
    - Allen, Robert (Box 78, Folder 18)
    - Allen, Robert Lee & Choros (Box 78, Folder 19)
    - Allers, Frarn (Box 78, Folder 20)
    - Alsop, Reck (Box 78, Folder 21)
    - Alva, Luigi (Box 78, Folder 22)
    - Alvary, Lorenzo (Box 78, Folder 23)
    - Amara, Lucine (Box 78, Folder 24)
    - Amaya, Carmen (Box 78, Folder 25)
    - Ameche, Don with Frederick, Pauline and Young (Box 78, Folder 26)
    - Anderson, Eddie (Box 78, Folder 27)
    - Anderson, Judith (Box 78, Folder 28)
    - Anderson, Judith & F. R. (Box 78, Folder 29)
    - Anderson, Marian (Box 78, Folder 30)
    - Anderson, Maxwell (Box 78, Folder 31)
    - Andrews, Frank (Box 78, Folder 32)
    - Angeles, Victoria de los (Box 78, Folder 33)
    - Anglin, Margaret (Box 78, Folder 34)
    - Annabella & Westley, Helen (Box 78, Folder 35)
    - Ansley, Charles (Box 78, Folder 36)
    - Apollon, Dave (Box 78, Folder 37)
    - La Argentina (Box 78, Folder 38)
    - Argentinita (Box 78, Folder 39)
    - Argo, Leif (Box 78, Folder 40)
    - Argus, Bill (Box 78, Folder 41)
    - Arliss, George (Box 78, Folder 42)
    - Armida (Box 78, Folder 43)
    - Armistead, Horace (Box 78, Folder 44)
    - Arnt, Charles (Box 78, Folder 45)
    - Art Photos (Box 78, Folder 46)
    - As Thousands Cheer (Box 78, Folder 47)
    - Asheratt, Peggy (Box 78, Folder 48)
    - Astaire (Box 78, Folder 49)
    - Astaire and Others (Box 78, Folder 50)
  - Robinson Photograph Collection (At - Ba)
    - Atherton, James and Monk, Allan (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Atlanta (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - Atwater, Edith (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Auer, Mischa (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - August, Joe (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - Aumont, Jean-Pierre (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - Avrora's Wedding (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - Austin, Gene (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - Autry, Gene (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - Ayers, Joe (Box 79, Folder 10)
    - Baccaloni, Salvatore (Box 79, Folder 11)
    - Baker, Benny (Box 79, Folder 12)
    - Balawin, Marcia (Box 79, Folder 13)
    - Ballet Russe de Monte Carlo (Box 79, Folder 14)
    - Bankhead, Tallulah (Box 79, Folder 15)
    - Un Ballo in Maschera (Box 79, Folder 16)
    - Baranova, Frina; & Dolin, Anton (Box 79, Folder 17)
    - Barber, Samuel and Bing, Rudolf (Box 79, Folder 18)
    - Il Barbiere di Siviglia (Box 79, Folder 19)
    - Bardelli, Cesare (Box 79, Folder 20)
    - Baroni, Giulio (Box 79, Folder 21)
    - Barrie, Elaine (Box 79, Folder 22)
    - Barry, Lloyd (Box 79, Folder 23)
    - Barrymore Family (Box 79, Folder 24)
    - Barrymore, Ethel (Box 79, Folder 25)
    - Barrymore, John (Box 79, Folder 26)
    - Barrymore, Lionel (Box 79, Folder 27)
    - Bartholomew, Freddy (Box 79, Folder 28)
    - Bartlett, Ethel & Robertson, Rae (Box 79, Folder 29)
    - Bartlett, Michael (Box 79, Folder 30)
    - Bastianini, Eltore (Box 79, Folder 31)
    - Batemar, Werner (Box 79, Folder 32)
    - Bauer, Harold (Box 79, Folder 33)
  - Robinson Photograph Collection (Be - Bu)
    - Beal, John (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Beatty, Clyde (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Le Beau Danube (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Beau Geste (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Behymer, L. E. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Belasco, David (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Bellamy, Ralph (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Belmont, Eleanor Robson (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Bennett, Constance (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - Benny, Joanie (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - Bergen, Edgar (Box 80, Folder 11)
    - Bergman, Ingrid (Box 80, Folder 12)
    - Bergner, Elisabeth with Sindair, Hugh (Box 80, Folder 13)
    - Bergonzi, Carlo (Box 80, Folder 14)
    - Berlin, Irving (Box 80, Folder 15)
    - Berman, Pandro S. (Box 80, Folder 16)
    - Bernini, Mario and others (Box 80, Folder 17)
    - Bickford, Charles (Box 80, Folder 18)
    - Bing, Rudolph (Box 80, Folder 19)
    - Bininger, Leo Charles (Box 80, Folder 20)
    - Bliss, Anthony and Family (Box 80, Folder 21)
    - Blodgett, dick and Marina (Box 80, Folder 22)
    - Bluebeard (Box 80, Folder 23)
    - Bogart, Humphrey (Box 80, Folder 24)
    - Le Boheme (Box 80, Folder 25)
    - Bohnen, Roman (Box 80, Folder 26)
    - Boland, Mary (Box 80, Folder 27)
    - Bolton Family (Box 80, Folder 28)
    - Bondi, Beulah (Box 80, Folder 29)
    - Bonelli, Richard (Box 80, Folder 30)
    - Bonheur, Chuck (Box 80, Folder 31)
    - Bynynge, Richard (Box 80, Folder 32)
    - Booth, Edwin (Box 80, Folder 33)
    - Bori, Lucrezia (Box 80, Folder 34)
    - Bowman, Patricia (Box 80, Folder 35)
    - Boyer, Charles (Box 80, Folder 36)
    - Brady, William A. (Box 80, Folder 37)
    - Brailowsky, Alexander (Box 80, Folder 38)
    - Brandon, Henry (Box 80, Folder 39)
    - Branzell, Karin (Box 80, Folder 40)
    - Brice, Fanny (Box 80, Folder 41)
    - Broderick, men & Moore, Victor (Box 80, Folder 42)
    - Broiles, Karen & Meluyn (Box 80, Folder 43)
    - Bronte, Peter (Box 80, Folder 44)
    - Brown, George (Box 80, Folder 45)
    - Brown, Johnny mark (Box 80, Folder 46)
    - Brown, Ray (Box 80, Folder 47)
    - Brownlee, John & Carla (Box 80, Folder 48)
    - Brzostouski, Melissa & Chet (Box 80, Folder 49)
    - Bruhn, Erik (Box 80, Folder 50)
    - Buchanan, Jane (Box 80, Folder 51)
    - Burbridge, Edward (Box 80, Folder 52)
    - Burgbauser, Hugo (Box 80, Folder 53)
    - Burke, Billie (Box 80, Folder 54)
    - Burke, Edmund (Box 80, Folder 55)
    - Burke, Georgia (Box 80, Folder 56)
    - Burrell, John (Box 80, Folder 57)
  - Robinson Photograph Collection (Ca - Cv)
    - Caballe, Montserrat (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Cacciapuoti, Giuseppe (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Callas, Maria (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - Calve, Emma (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - Cambon (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - Cantor, Eddie (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - Cantrell, Margaret (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - Capobianco, Tito (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - Capriccio Espagnol (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - Carlisle, Margaret (Box 81, Folder 10)
    - Carmen (Box 81, Folder 11)
    - Can-eras, Jose (Box 81, Folder 12)
    - Carrillo, Leo (Box 81, Folder 13)
    - Carroccia, Al (Box 81, Folder 14)
    - Carroll, Madeleine (Box 81, Folder 15)
    - Caruso, Enrico (Box 81, Folder 16)
    - Castle, Irene (Box 81, Folder 17)
    - Cathedral Choir (Box 81, Folder 18)
    - Cavalleria Rusticana (Box 81, Folder 19)
    - Lord and Lady Cavendish (Box 81, Folder 20)
    - Ceccato, Aldo and Eliana (Box 81, Folder 21)
    - Cehanousky, George (Box 81, Folder 22)
    - Chaliapire, Marina Freddi (Box 81, Folder 23)
    - Chaney, Lon & Meighan, Thomas (Box 81, Folder 24)
    - Chapin, Schuyier (Box 81, Folder 25)
    - Charles, Prince of Wales (Box 81, Folder 26)
    - Chatterton, Ruth (Box 81, Folder 27)
    - The Chautaugua (Box 81, Folder 28)
    - Chevalier, Maurice and MacDonald, Jeanette (Box 81, Folder 29)
    - Chookasian, Lili & Francis (Box 81, Folder 30)
    - Christians, Mady (Box 81, Folder 31)
    - Cimarosiana (Box 81, Folder 32)
    - Claire, Ina (Box 81, Folder 33)
    - Clark, Marguerite (Box 81, Folder 34)
    - Clark, Monsignor (Box 81, Folder 35)
    - Clements, Runcie Family (Box 81, Folder 36)
    - Cleva, Fausto (Box 81, Folder 37)
    - Clift, Montgomery with F. E. (Box 81, Folder 38)
    - Cohen, George (Box 81, Folder 39)
    - Colbert, Clandethe (Box 81, Folder 40)
    - Collier, Constance (Box 81, Folder 41)
    - Collinson, Ken (Box 81, Folder 42)
    - Colman, Ronald (Box 81, Folder 43)
    - Colzani, Anselmo (Box 81, Folder 44)
    - Concurrence (Box 81, Folder 45)
    - Connelly, Marc (Box 81, Folder 46)
    - Conrad, Karen & Kriza, John (Box 81, Folder 47)
    - Contes Russes (Box 81, Folder 48)
    - Cook, Claudia (Box 81, Folder 49)
    - Cook, Donald (Box 81, Folder 50)
    - Cooperman, Alvin and DePaul, Judith (Box 81, Folder 51)
    - Coppicus, F. C. (Box 81, Folder 52)
    - Le Cog d'Or (Box 81, Folder 53)
    - Cordon, Norman (Box 81, Folder 54)
    - Corellin, Franco (Box 81, Folder 55)
    - Corena, Fernando (Box 81, Folder 56)
    - Costello, Dulores (Box 81, Folder 57)
    - Cotrubas, Ileana (Box 81, Folder 58)
    - The Corered Wagon (Box 81, Folder 59)
    - Cowl, Jane (Box 81, Folder 60)
    - Crabbe, Buster (Box 81, Folder 61)
    - Crary, Clark (Box 81, Folder 62)
    - Craven, Frank (Box 81, Folder 63)
    - Craven, John (Box 81, Folder 64)
    - Crawford, Joan (Box 81, Folder 65)
    - Croft, Carl and Dorothy (Box 81, Folder 66)
    - Cromwell, John (Box 81, Folder 67)
    - Crooks, Richard (Box 81, Folder 68)
    - Crosman, Henrietta (Box 81, Folder 69)
    - Cross, Milton (Box 81, Folder 70)
    - Crossley Family (Box 81, Folder 71)
    - Cruz-Romo, Gilda (Box 81, Folder 72)
    - Curtiz, Michael (Box 81, Folder 73)
    - Cvejie, Beserka (Box 81, Folder 74)
  - Robinson Photograph Collection (Da - Fi)
    - Dabney, Augusta (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Dalis, Irene (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - Dal Monte, Toti (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - D'Amboise, Jacques, & Kent, Allegra (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - Damrosch, Walter (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - Daniels, Bebe (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - Darey, Emery (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - Dare, Phyllis (Box 82, Folder 8)
    - Dare, Zena (Box 82, Folder 9)
    - Davies, Marion (Box 82, Folder 10)
    - Davidson, Lawrence (Box 82, Folder 11)
    - Davis, Bette (Box 82, Folder 12)
    - Davis, Harold L. (Box 82, Folder 13)
    - Davis, Joe (Box 82, Folder 14)
    - Davis, Owen Sr. & Patterson, Elisabeth (Box 82, Folder 15)
    - Dean, Muysie (Box 82, Folder 16)
    - DeBasil, Col. W (Box 82, Folder 17)
    - De Hidalgo, Elvira (Box 82, Folder 18)
    - De Luca, Guiseppe (Box 82, Folder 19)
    - De Paolis, Alessio (Box 82, Folder 20)
    - De Reszke Singers (Box 82, Folder 21)
    - Del Castillo, Jorge (Box 82, Folder 22)
    - Del Monaco, Mario (Box 82, Folder 23)
    - Del Puente, Giweppe (Box 82, Folder 24)
    - Del Rio, Dolores (Box 82, Folder 25)
    - DellaCasa, Lisa (Box 82, Folder 26)
    - Destinn, Emmy (Box 82, Folder 27)
    - Dialogue of the Carmelites (Box 82, Folder 28)
    - Diamantopoulous, Mme. C.. (Box 82, Folder 29)
    - Diaz, Justin (Box 82, Folder 30)
    - Dick, Douglas (Box 82, Folder 31)
    - Dietrich, Marlene (Box 82, Folder 32)
    - Dietrich, Ray (Box 82, Folder 33)
    - Disney, Walt (Box 82, Folder 34)
    - Di Stetano, Giuseppe (Box 82, Folder 35)
    - Dolin, Anton & Markova, Alicia (Box 82, Folder 36)
    - Domingo, Placido (Box 82, Folder 37)
    - Don Cossack Chorus (Box 82, Folder 38)
    - Don Giovanni (Box 82, Folder 39)
    - Don Juan (Box 82, Folder 40)
    - Douglas, Kirk (Box 82, Folder 41)
    - Douglas, McLvyn with Gahagam, Helen and Peter (Box 82, Folder 42)
    - Downes, Edward (Box 82, Folder 43)
    - Downes, Edward (Box 82, Folder 44)
    - Doyle, Patsy (Box 82, Folder 45)
    - Dragoneth, Jessica (Box 82, Folder 46)
    - Draper, Paul (Box 82, Folder 47)
    - Dressler, Marie (Box 82, Folder 48)
    - Drew, George and Phyllis (Box 82, Folder 49)
    - Drew, John (Box 82, Folder 50)
    - Drummond, Harold (Box 82, Folder 51)
    - Duchin (Box 82, Folder 52)
    - Duke, Robert (Box 82, Folder 53)
    - Du Mond, Joe (Box 82, Folder 54)
    - Duna, Setti (Box 82, Folder 55)
    - Duncan, Mary (Box 82, Folder 56)
    - Dunn, Mignon (Box 82, Folder 57)
    - Dunne, Eithne (Box 82, Folder 58)
    - Dunne, Irene (Box 82, Folder 59)
    - Durante, Jimmy (Box 82, Folder 60)
    - Durbin, Deanna (Box 82, Folder 61)
    - Dushkin, Samuel (Box 82, Folder 62)
    - Dux, Claire (Box 82, Folder 63)
    - Eames, Emnia (Box 82, Folder 64)
    - Earl, Than and Phyllis (Box 82, Folder 65)
    - Earl, Seb (Box 82, Folder 66)
    - Eaton, Quaintance (Box 82, Folder 67)
    - Ebsen, Buddy (Box 82, Folder 68)
    - Eddy, Nelson (Box 82, Folder 69)
    - Edelmann, 0 Ho (Box 82, Folder 70)
    - Eggerth, Marta & Kupura, Jan (Box 82, Folder 71)
    - Eglevsky, Andre (Box 82, Folder 72)
    - Elements (Box 82, Folder 73)
    - Elias, Rosalind (Box 82, Folder 74)
    - Elman, Mischa (Box 82, Folder 75)
    - Elsom, Isabel (Box 82, Folder 76)
    - Enesco, Georges (Box 82, Folder 77)
    - English Singers (Box 82, Folder 78)